Ah, study and learn was over here, the option that I was searching for.
So let me do it again, but this time using the study and learn option.
So I ask and I turn the study and learn on and I send my command.
And this time I'm probably supposed to get something different, right?
It's not that different as you see, so this is pretty much the exact same thing that
I got over here, you know?
But it says that let's practice together, so do you want me to build a mini daily lesson
plan?
So this time it wanted to create me a plan, but this time it wants to practice with me,
you know, this is probably the only difference over here.
And the options are will lower as well, because you know, we're in the study and learn
mode, right?
And this is pretty much all that we have with this chatbot, just like any other chatbot
that we have, they are very similar, guys, very similar.